[
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000067", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 1 apple + 1 apple?", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000068", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 2 bananas + 2 bananas?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000069", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 3 carrots + 3 carrots?", "options": ["5","6","7"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000070", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 4 tomatoes + 4 tomatoes?", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000071", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 5 grapes + 5 grapes?", "options": ["9","10","11"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000072", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 6 cherries + 6 cherries?", "options": ["11","12","13"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000073", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 7 pears + 7 pears?", "options": ["13","14","15"], "correctAnswer": "14" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000074", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 8 potatoes + 8 potatoes?", "options": ["15","16","17"], "correctAnswer": "16" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000075", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 9 oranges + 9 oranges?", "options": ["17","18","19"], "correctAnswer": "18" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000076", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 10 corn + 10 corn?", "options": ["19","20","21"], "correctAnswer": "20" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000077", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 1 apple + 3 bananas?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000078", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 2 grapes + 4 grapes?", "options": ["5","6","7"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000079", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 3 carrots + 5 carrots?", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000080", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 4 tomatoes + 6 tomatoes?", "options": ["9","10","11"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000081", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 5 cherries + 7 cherries?", "options": ["11","12","13"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000082", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 6 pears + 8 pears?", "options": ["13","14","15"], "correctAnswer": "14" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000083", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 7 potatoes + 9 potatoes?", "options": ["15","16","17"], "correctAnswer": "16" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000084", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 8 oranges + 10 oranges?", "options": ["17","18","19"], "correctAnswer": "18" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000085", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 9 corn + 11 corn?", "options": ["19","20","21"], "correctAnswer": "20" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000086", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 10 apples + 12 apples?", "options": ["21","22","23"], "correctAnswer": "22" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000087", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 11 bananas + 13 bananas?", "options": ["23","24","25"], "correctAnswer": "24" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000088", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 12 grapes + 14 grapes?", "options": ["25","26","27"], "correctAnswer": "26" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000089", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 13 carrots + 15 carrots?", "options": ["27","28","29"], "correctAnswer": "28" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000090", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 14 tomatoes + 16 tomatoes?", "options": ["29","30","31"], "correctAnswer": "30" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000091", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 15 cherries + 17 cherries?", "options": ["31","32","33"], "correctAnswer": "32" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000092", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 16 pears + 18 pears?", "options": ["33","34","35"], "correctAnswer": "34" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000093", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 17 potatoes + 19 potatoes?", "options": ["35","36","37"], "correctAnswer": "36" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000094", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 18 oranges + 20 oranges?", "options": ["37","38","39"], "correctAnswer": "38" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000095", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 19 corn + 21 corn?", "options": ["39","40","41"], "correctAnswer": "40" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000096", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 20 apples + 22 apples?", "options": ["41","42","43"], "correctAnswer": "42" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000097", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 21 bananas + 23 bananas?", "options": ["43","44","45"], "correctAnswer": "44" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000098", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 22 grapes + 24 grapes?", "options": ["45","46","47"], "correctAnswer": "46" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000099", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 23 carrots + 25 carrots?", "options": ["47","48","49"], "correctAnswer": "48" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000100", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 24 tomatoes + 26 tomatoes?", "options": ["49","50","51"], "correctAnswer": "50" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000101", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 25 cherries + 27 cherries?", "options": ["51","52","53"], "correctAnswer": "52" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000102", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 26 pears + 28 pears?", "options": ["53","54","55"], "correctAnswer": "54" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000103", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 27 potatoes + 29 potatoes?", "options": ["55","56","57"], "correctAnswer": "56" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000104", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 28 oranges + 30 oranges?", "options": ["57","58","59"], "correctAnswer": "58" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000105", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 29 corn + 31 corn?", "options": ["59","60","61"], "correctAnswer": "60" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000106", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 30 apples + 32 apples?", "options": ["61","62","63"], "correctAnswer": "62" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000107", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 31 bananas + 33 bananas?", "options": ["63","64","65"], "correctAnswer": "64" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000108", "type": "addition", "question": "What is 32 grapes + 34 grapes?", "options": ["65","66","67"], "correctAnswer": "66" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000109", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 2 strawberries minus 1?", "options": ["0","1","2"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000110", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 3 watermelons minus 2?", "options": ["0","1","2"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000111", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 5 pineapples minus 3?", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000112", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 6 broccoli minus 4?", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000113", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 7 carrots minus 5?", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000114", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 8 apples minus 3?", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000115", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 9 bananas minus 4?", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000116", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 10 grapes minus 6?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000117", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 11 carrots minus 7?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000118", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 12 tomatoes minus 8?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000119", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 13 cherries minus 9?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000120", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 14 pears minus 10?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000121", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 15 potatoes minus 11?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000122", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 16 oranges minus 12?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000123", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 17 corn minus 13?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000124", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 18 apples minus 14?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000125", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 19 bananas minus 15?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000126", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 20 grapes minus 16?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000127", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 21 carrots minus 17?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000128", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 22 tomatoes minus 18?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000129", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 23 cherries minus 19?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000130", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 24 pears minus 20?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000131", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 25 potatoes minus 21?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000132", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 26 oranges minus 22?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000133", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 27 corn minus 23?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000134", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 28 apples minus 24?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000135", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 29 bananas minus 25?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000136", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 30 grapes minus 26?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000137", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 31 carrots minus 27?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000138", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 32 tomatoes minus 28?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000139", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 33 cherries minus 29?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000140", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 34 pears minus 30?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000141", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 35 potatoes minus 31?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000142", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 36 oranges minus 32?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000143", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 37 corn minus 33?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000144", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 38 apples minus 34?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000145", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 39 bananas minus 35?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000146", "type": "subtraction", "question": "What is 40 grapes minus 36?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000147", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 2 groups of 2 apples?", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000148", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 3 groups of 2 bananas?", "options": ["5","6","7"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000149", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 4 groups of 2 grapes?", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000150", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 5 groups of 2 carrots?", "options": ["9","10","11"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000151", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 6 groups of 2 tomatoes?", "options": ["11","12","13"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000152", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 7 groups of 2 cherries?", "options": ["13","14","15"], "correctAnswer": "14" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000153", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 8 groups of 2 pears?", "options": ["15","16","17"], "correctAnswer": "16" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000154", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 9 groups of 2 potatoes?", "options": ["17","18","19"], "correctAnswer": "18" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000155", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 10 groups of 2 oranges?", "options": ["19","20","21"], "correctAnswer": "20" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000156", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 11 groups of 2 corn?", "options": ["21","22","23"], "correctAnswer": "22" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000157", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 2 groups of 3 apples?", "options": ["5","6","7"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000158", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 3 groups of 3 bananas?", "options": ["8","9","10"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000159", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 4 groups of 3 grapes?", "options": ["11","12","13"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000160", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 5 groups of 3 carrots?", "options": ["14","15","16"], "correctAnswer": "15" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000161", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 6 groups of 3 tomatoes?", "options": ["17","18","19"], "correctAnswer": "18" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000162", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 7 groups of 3 cherries?", "options": ["20","21","22"], "correctAnswer": "21" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000163", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 8 groups of 3 pears?", "options": ["23","24","25"], "correctAnswer": "24" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000164", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 9 groups of 3 potatoes?", "options": ["26","27","28"], "correctAnswer": "27" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000165", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 10 groups of 3 oranges?", "options": ["29","30","31"], "correctAnswer": "30" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000166", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 11 groups of 3 corn?", "options": ["32","33","34"], "correctAnswer": "33" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000167", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 2 groups of 4 apples?", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000168", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 3 groups of 4 bananas?", "options": ["11","12","13"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000169", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 4 groups of 4 grapes?", "options": ["15","16","17"], "correctAnswer": "16" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000170", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 5 groups of 4 carrots?", "options": ["19","20","21"], "correctAnswer": "20" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000171", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 6 groups of 4 tomatoes?", "options": ["23","24","25"], "correctAnswer": "24" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000172", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 7 groups of 4 cherries?", "options": ["27","28","29"], "correctAnswer": "28" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000173", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 8 groups of 4 pears?", "options": ["31","32","33"], "correctAnswer": "32" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000174", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 9 groups of 4 potatoes?", "options": ["35","36","37"], "correctAnswer": "36" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000175", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 10 groups of 4 oranges?", "options": ["39","40","41"], "correctAnswer": "40" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000176", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 11 groups of 4 corn?", "options": ["43","44","45"], "correctAnswer": "44" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000177", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 2 groups of 5 apples?", "options": ["9","10","11"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000178", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 3 groups of 5 bananas?", "options": ["14","15","16"], "correctAnswer": "15" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000179", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 4 groups of 5 grapes?", "options": ["19","20","21"], "correctAnswer": "20" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000180", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 5 groups of 5 carrots?", "options": ["24","25","26"], "correctAnswer": "25" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000181", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 6 groups of 5 tomatoes?", "options": ["29","30","31"], "correctAnswer": "30" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000182", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 7 groups of 5 cherries?", "options": ["34","35","36"], "correctAnswer": "35" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000183", "type": "multiplication", "question": "What is 8 groups of 5 pears?", "options": ["39","40","41"], "correctAnswer": "40" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000184", "type": "division", "question": "Share 6 mangoes between 2 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000185", "type": "division", "question": "Share 8 pumpkins between 4 friends.", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000186", "type": "division", "question": "Share 9 cucumbers between 3 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000187", "type": "division", "question": "Share 10 apples between 5 friends.", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000188", "type": "division", "question": "Share 12 bananas between 4 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000189", "type": "division", "question": "Share 14 grapes between 7 friends.", "options": ["1","2","3"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000190", "type": "division", "question": "Share 16 carrots between 4 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000191", "type": "division", "question": "Share 18 tomatoes between 6 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000192", "type": "division", "question": "Share 20 cherries between 5 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000193", "type": "division", "question": "Share 24 pears between 8 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000194", "type": "division", "question": "Share 30 potatoes between 6 friends.", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000195", "type": "division", "question": "Share 36 oranges between 9 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000196", "type": "division", "question": "Share 40 corn between 8 friends.", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000197", "type": "division", "question": "Share 12 apples between 3 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000198", "type": "division", "question": "Share 15 bananas between 5 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000199", "type": "division", "question": "Share 18 grapes between 6 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000200", "type": "division", "question": "Share 20 carrots between 4 friends.", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000201", "type": "division", "question": "Share 24 tomatoes between 6 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000202", "type": "division", "question": "Share 30 cherries between 10 friends.", "options": ["2","3","4"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000203", "type": "division", "question": "Share 32 pears between 8 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000204", "type": "division", "question": "Share 36 potatoes between 9 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000205", "type": "division", "question": "Share 40 oranges between 10 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000206", "type": "division", "question": "Share 48 corn between 12 friends.", "options": ["3","4","5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000207", "type": "division", "question": "Share 50 apples between 10 friends.", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000208", "type": "division", "question": "Share 54 bananas between 9 friends.", "options": ["5","6","7"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000209", "type": "division", "question": "Share 60 grapes between 12 friends.", "options": ["4","5","6"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000210", "type": "division", "question": "Share 64 carrots between 8 friends.", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000211", "type": "division", "question": "Share 72 tomatoes between 9 friends.", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000212", "type": "division", "question": "Share 80 cherries between 10 friends.", "options": ["7","8","9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000213", "type": "division", "question": "Share 90 pears between 15 friends.", "options": ["5","6","7"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
  { "_id": "000000000000000000000214", "type": "division", "question": "Share 100 potatoes between 10 friends.", "options": ["9","10","11"], "correctAnswer": "10" }
]